...and Dr. Winkle just ripped
the sign-up sheet off the wall.
It wasn't an official sign-up sheet.
He printed it...
(Leslie:)...and he put his name down
on every slot for the next six months.
(Sheldon:)If it is a crime to ensure
the university's resources...
(Sheldon:)...are not being squandered
chasing subatomic wild geese...
(Sheldon:)...then I plead guilty.
[PHONE RINGING]
(Sheldon:)Oh, Penny.
- You need to get that, Dr. Cooper?
- God, no.
(Leslie:)Don't turn it off. You might miss
your call from Nobel...
(Leslie:)...letting you know you've been nominated
as dumb-ass laureate of the year.
(Sheldon:)Oh, yeah, well,
you wouldn't even be nominated.
I have a series of important multi-loop
calculations and simulations to run.
She's reducing irrelevant data,
making a mock...
[PHONE RINGS]
(Gablehauser(as phone rings):)Excuse me.
(Scene:)Gablehauser.
(Gablehauser(as phone rings):)It's for you.